well today and that is on the back of
earnings is ICI Lombard and that is up
almost 4% now after its fourth quarter
results Yash is in with the fine print
Yash how are the numbers I guess the
stock is reacting to some good numbers
well Norma hormas you spoke about things
being noisy and as far as the quar for
results for ICC Lombard are concerned
they were quite noisy uh we've been
talking about these numbers month on
month and telling our viewers that ICS
Lombard's premium collection was
constantly outperforming the industry
average and the same has reflected in
the fourth quarter as well so as far as
the fourth quarter net earn premium is
concerned for ICI Lombard That Grew by
about 177% the industry average here
growth was just about 133% so about 400
basis points outperformance to the
industry average another uh important
aspect and a positive one was the
underwriting loss in Q4 that reduced by
about 7 and 1 half% uh the loss
underwriting loss came in at about 232
CR rupees versus 251 CR rupes and the
most important aspect combined ratio
that also lowered in the fourth quarter
coming at about 102.2 versus
104.2 the management has given a very
bullish stance as far as the combined
ratio is concerned they've said by
quarter 4 fi25 that is exactly one year
from now they expect to reduce combined
ratio by another 50 basis points and
doing it at already good levels that is
102.2 uh would be taken very very
positively as far as as balancing of
portfolios is concerned Lombard has done
that uh very well in the fourth quarter
uh two segments motor and fire where the
premium growth hasn't been very strong
they've sort of looked at uh you know
improving the underwriting performance
and health has come out where the
premium growth has been very strong so
of course underwriting performance
getting improved in two large verticals
premium growth coming about in one
vertical all of that balancing
portfolios very well and the numbers
look strong for the company
thank you very much for that